charlieapp.com 2019-06-20

# Detective by Charlie App | Press

_Effective as of December 15, 2017_

Your privacy and data security are important to us. As users of countless applications ourselves, we know how important it is to trust the apps and websites we all use. As a result, we abide by strict internal processes developed to maintain your data in a secure environment.

Detective by Charlie uses private and publicly available data to provide you with information on your prospects. We pull information from across the web, from your Connected Accounts and from our data partners.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to explain (1) what personal data we collect, (2) how we use the data, and (3) who we share the data with.

## What and Why

We may collect and use the following information to provide, improve and protect our Services:

### Personal Data

As part of assisting our customers with prospecting, we may collect the following personal data:

  * Email addresses
  * Names
  * Public Twitter profiles
  * Public LinkedIn profiles

In addition, we may collect the following personal data from users who create an account with our service:

  * Information about you from your Salesforce account, including the following: your email, your manager's name and email, your role, your department, your division, your photo and your title.

If you wish to exercise any rights you may have to access, correct, migrate or delete your personal data please contact us at dataprivacy@detective.io

### Connected Accounts

When you use Detective by Charlie, you may grant us access to third-party applications like Salesforce. We query, store, process, and transmit information related to your Connected Accounts. When using data from Connected Accounts, we distinguish between

  * **Public data** , which is information that users have chosen to make public on the Internet, and which anyone can find using one of the major search engines. We aggregate public data, take into account corrections and feedback to ensure accuracy, and show this information to everyone who uses Detective by Charlie. 
  * **Private data** , which is privileged information to which only you have access. We may need to process this data (only as listed in the “With Whom” section; however, the private data itself will never be displayed to any other Detective by Charlie user. 

### Usage

We collect information from and about the devices you use to access the Services. This includes things like IP addresses, the type of browser and device you use, the web page you visited before coming to our sites, and identifiers associated with your devices. Your devices (depending on their settings) may also transmit location information to the Services.

### Cookies and Pixel Tags

We use cookies and pixel tags to provide, improve, protect and promote our Services. For example, cookies help us with things like remembering your username for your next visit, understanding how you are interacting with our Services, and improving them based on that information. You can set your browser to not accept cookies, but this may limit your ability to use the Services.

## How

### Research & Prospecting

We may access your Connected Accounts to assist with researching the people and companies you are prospecting. For example, we may use your Salesforce account to fetch information about the Accounts and Contacts you are prospecting.

### Deletion

If you would like to delete your account, we will delete all of your private data. This includes information associated with your account. Please note: (1) there might be some latency in deleting this information from our servers and back-up storage; and (2) we may retain this information if necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements. To delete your account, contact us at support@detective.io.

### Security

We have team members dedicated to keeping your information secure and testing for vulnerabilities. We also continue to work on features to keep your information safe. However, while we attempt to protect all information you send to us and we maintain to provide Detective by Charlie to you, please note that no connection through the Internet and data storage facilities are entirely immune from unauthorized hacking and access, and so you should use Detective by Charlie with discretion. You can help us by protecting your username and password and using Detective by Charlie only through secure networks.

## With Whom

Your private data will be kept secure and private as detailed above. It may need to be processed by other people or third party purposes. We will only share such information for the following purposes.

### Others working for Charlie

For quality and technical support purposes, select Charlie employees may review your data. These employees will access your information only to perform tasks on behalf of and in compliance with this Privacy Policy.

### Service Providers

Detective by Charlie uses trusted third party service providers to help us provide, improve, protect, and promote our Services (for example, Google Analytics uses cookies to help us understand how users interact with the Charlie website). These third parties will access your information only to perform tasks on our behalf and in compliance with this Privacy Policy.

### Anonymized & Aggregated Data

We may share aggregated or otherwise non-identifiable information, like Detective usage statistics. For example, we may write a blog post using statistics like “The average engineer takes most meetings in the morning.”

### Law & Order

We may disclose your information to third parties if we determine that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with the law; (b) protect any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Detective by Charlie or our users; or (d) protect Charlie's property rights.

Stewardship of your data is critical to us and a responsibility that we embrace. We believe that our users' data should receive the same legal protections regardless of whether it's stored on our services or on their home computer's hard drive. We'll abide by the following principles when receiving, scrutinizing and responding to government requests for our users' data:

  * Be transparent 
  * Fight blanket requests 
  * Protect all users 
  * Provide trusted services 

### Changes

If we are involved in a reorganization, merger, acquisition or sale of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that deal. We will notify you (for example, via a message to the email address associated with your account) of any such deal and outline your choices in that event.

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post the most current version on our website. Please visit this page from time to time to check for updates. If a revision meaningfully reduces your rights, we will notify you.

### International

If you use or access Detective by Charlie from a country outside the United States, you understand and agree that your information will be collected, maintained and processed on servers located both in and outside the United States.

### Children

Detective by Charlie is not intended for or directed to children under the age of 13. If we become aware that someone under the age of 13 has provided their personally identifiable information, we will promptly delete that information.

### Contact

Have questions or concerns about Charlie, our Services and privacy? Contact us at support@detective.io.
